Register to The E.Y. Harburg Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Harburgiana, 1929-1968; Series II
  - Correspondence
    - General Correspondence
      - Warner, Jack, 1941 Feb 18; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - to Warner, Jack, 1941 Feb 19; carbon (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Weisman, Davis (forwarded by Irving Hoffman), 1945 Jan 15; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - to Weisman, David, 1945 Feb 11; carbon (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Weisman, David, 1945 Feb 17; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Wolpin, Edward A., 1942 Nov 16; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - to Wolpin, Edward A., 1943 Jul 17; carbon (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Wood, Audrey, 1963 Nov 26; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Woodthorpe, Peter, 1968 Feb 2; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Wouk, Herman (as Ensign, U.S.N.R.), [1943] May 1; typed letter signed, microfiche (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - to Wouk, Herman, 1943 Jun 1; carbon (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Wouk, Herman, [1943?]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
    - Correspondence on Rhymes for the Irreverent
      - McCormick, Ken, 1963 Nov 7; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - McCormick, Ken, 1964 Jan 13; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Fisher, Richard B. (Manager, McGraw-Hill) to Mason, Jerry, 1964 Jun 2; carbon (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Fischer, Stephen M. to (Grossman Publishers), 1965 Jun 17; carbon (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Berlin, Irving, 1965 Dec 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Rodgers, Richard, 1965 Dec 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Buchwald, Art, 1965 Dec 27; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Jablonski, Edward C., 1965 Dec 29; autograph letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Marshall, Armina, [1966] Jan 31; autograph letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Fulbright, J.W. (Senator), 1966 Feb 14; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Sinatra, Frank, 1966 Feb 17; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Morse, Senator Wayne, 1966 Feb 28; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Perlman, Jess to [?], Harold, 1966 Jul 2; autograph letter signed, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - MacKenty, John G., 1966 Aug 10; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Kopaz, Chester, 1967 Apr 27; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Schenker, Joel W. to Meltzer, Herman, 1968 Jun 28; carbon (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Bugbee, Louise Aldrich (columnist, Vineyard Gazette), 1968 Jul 6; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Williams, Frederick C., 1968 Jul 12; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Bugbee, Louise Aldrich, [1968?]; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - [Colbert?] (Vineyard Gazette), [1968?]; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 192)
      - Neville, Jean, [no date]; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - ASCAP Correspondence
      - Hubbell, Raymond (Chairman of Membership Committee), 1932 Apr 7; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene (President), 1933 Oct 11; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1934 Jan 15; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1934 Mar 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1934 Jul 2; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1934 Dec 26; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1935 Jan 4; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Mill, E.C. (Chairman, Administrative Committee), 1938 Dec 12; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
        (Enclosure: Publicity circular on E.Y. Harburg, etc.)
      - Buck, Gene, 1939 Oct 10; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1939 Oct 10; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1941 Dec 19; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to Rosenberg, Sylvia (secretary to Gene Buck), 1942 Jan 28; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Rosenberg, Sylvia, 1942 Feb 3; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
        (Enclosure: ASCAP list of works by E.Y. Harburg)
      - to ASCAP, 1942 Apr 8; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to Buck, Gene, 1942 May 11; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Buck, Gene, 1942 Jul 1; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to ASCAP, 1943 Jan 14; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Rosenberg, Sylvia (Secretary to Deems Taylor), 1943 Jan 22; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to Rosenberg, Sylvia, 1943 Feb 15; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Rosenberg, Sylvia, 1943 Mar 12; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to ASCAP (Attn: S. Rosenberg), 1943 Mar 19; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Klingman, A.W., 1943 Apr 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to Klingman, A.W., 1943 May 4; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to ASCAP, 1943 Jun 10; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - to ASCAP, 1943 Sep 22; carbon (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Paine, John G., 1944 Dec 15; photocopy (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Bridgman, Carol (ASCAP Index Department), 1945 Apr 24; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Taylor, Deems (re: Television rights), 1945 Oct 1; contract (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Taylor, Deems, 1946 May; photocopy (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Taylor, Deems, 1947 Jan 14; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Nelson, James (Chairman, The Players Pipe Night Comm.), 1964 Feb 17; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Lindsay, Howard (for The Players), 1964 Mar 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
      - Gottlieb, Herbert N., 1968 Aug 8; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 193)
    - Miscellaneous Professional Correspondence
      - Spitzer, Henry M., 1935 Jun 6; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - Starr, Herman, 1942 Feb 5; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - to Skadron, Bernard, 1947 Apr 3; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - to Skadron, Bernard, 1947 May 2; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - to Skadron, Bernard, 1947 Nov 14; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - to Skadron, Bernard, 1948 Mar 23; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - Rosen, Paul A., 1960 Oct 18; memo, signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
        (Enclosure: typed letter signed from Leslie Winik, International Telemeter Co.)
      - Meltzer, Herman I., 1961 Aug 10; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - Meltzer, Herman I., 1967 Jan 11; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - Kane, Joel (Secretary, Writers Guild of America, Inc.), 1968 Jan 9; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
      - Meltzer, Herman I., 1968 Jul 25; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 194)
    - Political & Philanthropical Correspondence
      - to LaGuardia, Mayor Fiorello, 1941 Apr 24; carbon (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Blaine, James G. (Chairman, United China Relief, Inc.), 1941 May 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Page, James R., et al. (President, Los Angeles Community Welfare Federation), 1941 Nov 12; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Edwards, C.G. (Director, D.R., L.A. Community Welfare Federation), 1941 Nov 15; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Shubert, John (Editor & Chairman, The Writers & Material Committee, U.S.O. Camp Shows, Inc.), 1942 Jul 22; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Inglis, Frances (Assistant to David O. Selznick), 1942 Aug 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Luce, Henry R. to Selznick, David O., 1942 Aug 10; carbon (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Herod, W. R. (President, United China Relief), 1942 Aug 11; carbon (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Shubert, John (Editor & Chairman, The Writers & Material Committee, U.S.O. Camp Shows, Inc.), 1942 Sep 24; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Olson, Culbert L. (Governor of California), 1942 Nov 17; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Andrew[s], Bob, 1943 Apr 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Connelly, Marc (Writers Congress), 1943 Dec 8; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Roberts, Homer B., Major, C.M.P. (War Department Bureau of Public Relations), 1944 May 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - to Selznick, David O., 1944 May 18; carbon, signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Patterson, Ellis E., 1944 May 18; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Young, Harold (Assistant to U.S. Vice President), 1944 Jun 7; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Swerling, Jo (President, Rodeo Drive Democratic Committee of California), 1944 Sep 6; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Novik, M.S. (Director, City of N.Y. Municipal Broadcasting System), 1944 Nov 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Wyatt, Wilson W. (Mayor, Louisville, Kentucky) to Schacter, Harry W., 1944 Dec 6; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Lilienthal, David E. (Chairman, Tennessee Valley Authority), 1944 Dec 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Lilienthal, David E., 1945 Jan 1; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Hammerstein II, Oscar, 1945 Jan 15; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Lilienthal, David E., 1945 Jan 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Schachter, Harry, 1945 Jan 25; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Gridges, Harry, 1945 Jun 18; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Kenny, Robert W. (Attorney General, California), 1945 Aug 4; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Lilienthal, David E., 1945 Aug 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - to Wagner, Senator Robert (U.S. Senate), 1945 Aug 31; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Connolly, Captain J.P. (Director of Special Services, Department of National Defense, Canada), 1946 Jan 31; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 195)
      - Sun Yat-sen, Mme., [1946 Feb 20]; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Einstein, Albert (as Chairman, Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists), 1946 Jun 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Bakst, Fan (American Birobidjan Committee), 1947 Apr 17; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Field, Frederick V., 1948 Feb 5; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Poulson, Harper, 1948 Feb 16; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Magil, Abe, 1948 Feb 17; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Eisen, Leo (President, Class of 1918, College of City of N.Y.), 1948 Mar 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Lane, Burton [re: blacklist], 1950 Nov 22; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Lane, Burton [re: blacklist], 1950 Nov 28; typed letter, draft (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Lane, Burton [re: blacklist], 1950 Nov 28; carbon, draft (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Lane, Burton [re: blacklist], 1950 Nov 29; carbon [final draft?] (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Rubin, [?] (Legal Department, MGM) [re: blacklist], 1950 Dec 25; typed letter, draft (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Wolinsky, Sylvia (Fair Employment Practice Commission, Philadelphia), 1951 Apr 24; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Larric, Ivy (Mrs.) (Larric Theatre Party Bureau), 1951 Jun 13; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Rice, Elmer (The Authors League of America, Inc. Enclosure: questionnaire on blacklisting), 1952 Feb 21; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to The Authors League of America, Inc., 1952 Feb 26; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Lane, Burton [re: blacklist], 1952 Jun 11; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Freeman, Y. Frank (Paramount Pictures) [re: blacklist], 1952 Aug 4; carbon & photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to American Civil Liberties Union, 1953 Nov 19; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Burgum, Edwin Berry (Honorary Chairman, N.Y. Council of the Arts, Sciences & Professions, Inc.), [1954]; typed letter, form (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - [Crane?], Sylvia, 1961 Dec 15; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Piel, Gerard (re: Assemblyman Mark Lane), 1962 Mar 13; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Gallagher, Buell G. (President, The City College), 1962 Apr 17; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Livingston, Bob (Damon Runyon Memorial Fund for Cancer Research, Inc.), 1962 Apr 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Udell, Jerome I. (President, The City College Fund), 1962 Dec 5; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Gallagher, Buell G., 1963 Jan 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Topol, Julius (Chairman, N.Y. Council for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1964 Apr 27; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Wilkins, Roy (National Association for the Advancement of Colored People), 1964 May 7; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Kahn, Kermit, 1964 May 22; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
        (Enclosure: review of "Freedom Spectacular," The Hollywood Reporter)
      - Smith, Hamlin Dunlap (Headmaster, The Oakland School), 1967 Jun 29; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Kahan, Phyllis (Los Angeles Friends of Senator Wayne Morse), 1967 Oct 2; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Kahan, Phyllis, 1967 Oct 13; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Fanu, Albert L. (Artist Director, Harlem Dramatic Arts Theatre), 1967 Oct 21; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Ziferstein, I., [1967] Oct 23; autograph letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Kahan, Phyllis, 1967 Oct 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Shane, Joseph D., 1967 Oct 30; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Udell, Jerome I. (The City College), 1968 Jan 17; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Stamler, Jeremiah (M.D.), 1968 Apr 15; autograph letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Ryan, William R. (N.Y. Congressman), 1968 May 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - to Student Mobilization Committee, 1968 Jul 2; carbon, signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
      - Solicitation letter from E.Y. Harburg for Israeli School, Givat Haviva, [no date]; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Miscellaneous Institutional Correspondence
      - to Bantam Books, Inc., 1953 Mar 4; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Bob Waystaff, Producer, 1962 Aug 31; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - CBS Television Network; Sid Garfield, Director, Special Projects, 1968 May 1; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Crown Publishers, Inc., Herbert Michelman, 1966 Apr 27; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - to Jamaica Tourist Bureau; Philip Benfield, 1953 Jan 16; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - John H. Finley School, N.Y.; Martha Froehlich, 1964 Apr 8; autograph letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - to Froehlich, Martha; John H. Finley School, 1964 Apr 22; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - to pupils of John H. Finley School, 1964 Apr 22; carbon, photocopy (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Little Red School House; Randolph B. Smith, 1962 Apr 12; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Museum of the City of New York; Sam Pearce, Curator, 1966 Dec 29; telegram (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Museum of the City of New York, Friends of the Theatre & Music Collection Sam Pearce, Curator, 1968 Apr 16; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - to Sam Pearce, Curator, Museum of the City of New York, 1968 Apr 23; carbon (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - The Nation magazine; Carey Williams, 1962 Sep 10; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - to National Educational Television; Eleanor Solomon from Janice Clayton, 1962 Jun 27; carbon (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - New York City Board of Education; Elias Lieberman, Assoc. Superintendent to George L. Paley, [no date]; carbon (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - North American Philips Company, Inc., 1968 Jul 23; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Variety magazine; Abel Green, Editor, 1964 Feb 5; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - WBC Productions, Inc.; Mert Koplin, Exec. Producer of "P.M.", 1962 Jun 1; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Young Women's Christian Association; Helen H. Talbot, Program Director, Teenage Department to Earl Robinson, 1949 Nov 15; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
      - Y.W.C.A.; Helen Talbot, 1949 Nov 21; typed letter signed (Box 23, Folder 197)
  - Programs, News Clippings, Reviews
    [N.B. The items in Folders 198-201 are photocopies from the scrapbooks. See the Introduction to Series II, page 65.]
    - Scrapbook No. 1 Items related to musical productions (Box 28, Folder 198)
      Eveready Hour Revue: "The Local Boy Makes Good"
      Earl Carroll's Sketch Book
      Garrick Gaieties
      Accidentally Yours
      Earl Carroll's Vanities
      The Vanderbilt Revue
      Billy Rose's Crazy Quilt
      Ballyhoo of 1932
      Americana
      Walk a Little Faster
      Moonlight and Pretzels
      Take a Chance
      Ziegfeld Follies of 1934
      (Miscellaneous clippings from the 1930s)
      Life Begins at 8:40
      The Show Is On
    - Scrapbook No. 2 Items related to musical productions (Box 28, Folder 199)
      The Singing Kid
      Stage Struck
      Hooray for What!
      The Wizard of Oz
      Hold On To Your Hats
      (Miscellaneous Harburgiana)
    - Scrapbook No. 3 Items related to musical productions (Box 28, Folder 200)
      Bloomer Girl
      Meet the Pople
      Finian's Rainbow
    - Scrapbook No. 4 Items related to musical productions (Box 28, Folder 201)
      Flahooley
      Jamaica
      The Happiest Girl in the World
      Darling of the Day
    - Original items preserved from the scrapbooks (Box 24, Folder 202)
      - Sixteen-page promotional brochure for Hold On To Your Hats, [1940] (Box 24, Folder 202)
        (from Scrapbook No. 2, page 21, recto) -- 1 page
      - Certificates from "The Billboard Fourth Annual Donaldson Awards," for Finian's Rainbow, [1947] (Box 24, Folder 202)
        (Best Musical, Best Book)
        (from Scrapbook No. 3, page 10, recto & verso) -- 2 pages
      - Eight-page program booklet from the Gaiety Theatre [Dublin] production of Finian's Rainbow, [1964] (Box 24, Folder 202)
        (from Scrapbook No. 3, page 19, recto) -- 1 page
      - Memo from Gary Stevens, 1965 Dec 23, regarding a press clipping about Rhymes for the Irreverent (Box 24, Folder 202)
        (typed letter, signed)
        (from Scrapbook No. 3, page 27, recto) -- 1 page
      - Memo from Philip Langner, 1967 Oct 15, regarding a press clipping about Darling of the Day, [1968] (Box 24, Folder 202)
        (holograph letter, signed)
        (from Scrapbook No. 4, page 17, recto) -- 1 page
    - Eveready Hour (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Newspaper review of "The Mayor of Hogan's Alley" (1929) -- 1 page
    - Ballyhoo of 1932 (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Atlantic City, N.J. playbill, 1932 Aug 10 -- 1 page
    - Americana (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Royalty agreement; Harms, Inc. Signed by Jay Gorney & E.Y. Harburg -- 1 page
    - Walk a Little Faster (Box 25, Folder 203)
      News clipping, photocopied -- 3 pages
    - Take a Chance (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Advertisement quoting, "It's Only a Paper Moon" -- 1 page
    - Ziegfeld Follies & Life Begins at 8:40 (Box 25, Folder 203)
      News clippings, mounted -- 4 pages
    - Broadway Gondolier (Box 25, Folder 203)
      News clippings -- 2 pages
    - Hooray For What! (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Playbills: N.Y., 1937 Dec 6 Philadelphia, 1937 Nov 16 -- 2 pages
    - Hooray For What! (Box 28, Folder 221)
      Broadway Advertisement Photograph (Winter Garden Theatre, 1937-1938[?])
    - The Wizard of Oz (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Publicity, clippings, junior high school production program -- 12 pages
      [See also: Publicity brochure for Hold On To Your Hats, from Scrapbook No. 2, in Box 24, Folder 202]
    - Bloomer Girl (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Souvenir program, N.Y. -- 1 page
      Feature article, "Pic" magazine, 1944 Nov 21 (pp. 30û33) -- 1 page
      Article on Agnes de Mille, The New Yorker, 1946 Sep 14 (pp. 33-45) -- 1 page
      Fragment of newspaper review -- 1 page
    - California (Box 25, Folder 203)
      Feature article, Liberty magazine [1946?] -- 1 page
    - Finian's Rainbow (Original Broadway production) (Box 25, Folder 204)
      Photocopy of program -- 1 page
      Review, The Saturday Review, 1947 Feb 15 (3 pp.) -- 1 page
      Clipping re: Donaldson Awards, PM magazine, 1947 Aug 17 (1 p.) -- 1 page
      [See also: Donaldson Award certificates, from Scrapbook No. 3, in Box 24, Folder 202]
      Complete stage play, reprinted in Theatre Arts magazine, 1949 Jan (20 pp.) -- 1 page
    - Finian's Rainbow (N.Y. City revivals) (Box 25, Folder 204)
      N.Y. City Center Light Opera Company revival, directed by Jean Dalrymple, 1960 May: Souvenir album -- 1 page
      Variety review, 1960 May 4 (1 p.) -- 1 page
      N.Y. Herald Tribune review, 1960 May 13, photocopy (1 p.) -- 1 page
      Sunday News review, 1960 May 29, orig. clipping & 2 photocopies -- 3 pages
      Sunday News announcement re: City Center production's transfer to Broadway, 1960 May 22 -- 1 page
    - Finian's Rainbow (N.Y. City revivals) (Box 25, Folder 204)
      N.Y. City Center Light Opera Company revival, directed by Jean Dalrymple, 1967 Apr
      Souvenir program -- 1 page
      Manhattan East, news clipping of review by John Lahr, 1967 Apr 13 (1 p.) -- 1 page
    - Finian's Rainbow (Regional and touring productions, 1948-1968) (Box 25, Folder 205)
      - Nixon Theatre, Pittsburgh, [Pennsylvania], [1948] (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Photocopy of clipping, Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1948 Dec 29 (1 p.) -- 1 page
      - Greek Theatre, Los Angeles, California, [1950?] (Box 25, Folder 205)
      - [N.Y. State?], [1950s?] (Box 25, Folder 205)
      - Valley Forge Music Fair, [1956 Aug 27] (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Publicity -- 1 page
      - Jamaica High School, Jamaica, N.Y. City, 1958 May 2-3 (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Program -- 1 page
      - U.C.L.A., Los Angeles, California, 1961 May 10-13 (Box 25, Folder 205)
      - LaSalle College, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1963 [Jun-Jul?] (Box 25, Folder 205)
        The Evening Bulletin review, Philadelphia, 1963 Jul 5, 2 copies -- 2 copies
      - Anaheim Theatre, Los Angeles, California, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Newspaper review -- 1 page
      - Miami-Dade Junior College, Florida, 1966 Mar (Box 25, Folder 205)
        The Miami Herald, 1966 Mar 27 -- 1 page
      - Cellar Door Players, Larchmont, N.Y., 1967 Aug 25 (Box 25, Folder 205)
        N.Y. Times, 1967 Aug 26 -- 1 page
      - Bonfils Theatre, Denver, Colorado, 1967 Oct 12 (Box 25, Folder 205)
        The Denver Post, 1967 Oct 13 -- 1 page
      - Ann Arbor Civic Theatre, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1968 Apr 10-14 (Box 25, Folder 205)
        The Ann Arbor News, review, 1968 Apr 11 -- 1 page
      - The Fort Totten Little Theatre, Fort Totten, North Dakota, [1968 Jul 4-Aug 11] (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Clippings & publicity poster -- 4 pages
      - Hollywood Repertory Theatre, California, [no date] (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Clipping -- 1 page
      - Youth Choirs, Riverdale Presbyterian Church, [no date] (Box 25, Folder 205)
      - Howard University, Washington, D.C., [no date] (Box 25, Folder 205)
        Photograph of cast & E.Y. Harburg -- 1 page
    - Finian's Rainbow (International productions) (Box 25, Folder 206)
      - New Shakespeare Theatre, Liverpool, England, 1957 Dec 27 (Box 25, Folder 206)
        Photocopies of news clippings -- 1 page [large sheet]
      - London revival, [1959?] (Box 25, Folder 206)